Sebastian Vazquez

Production
Coordinator /
Manager

_

Introduction

vazq.seba@gmail.com

+1 (437) 353-8810

sebastian-vazquez.com.ar linkedin.com/in/sebavazquez

1532 - 525 Adelaide St W Toronto, ON, M5V 0N7

I'm a 26 years old Production Coordinator/Manager with 3+ years of experience in 3D animation studios and video game companies from Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Graduated as Image and Sound Designer from Universidad de Palermo, I moved to Toronto, Ontario, in May 2018 with an **open work permit and am currently seeking for job opportunities.**

I'm an ambitious and passionate professional, who's fully dedicated to the audiovisual industry, from film to video games and TV series. I have a solid foundation on CGI, having learnt through formal education and by myself. This allows me to interact smoothly from a technical and creative point of view in any production.

I study everyday of my life to have a broad set of skills, from technical aspects to production, marketing, team management and product development. My main goal is always focused on managing and delivering products and projects with the highest quality standards, **whilst getting things done.**

Experience

LemonChili / Technical Production Coordinator

FEBRUARY 2016 - APRIL 2018 BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA

Worked as a link between the programming, art and game design departments, managing teams and ensuring quality standards and deadlines are met on each assignment, as well as leading the 3D department.

Worked closely with the marketing and social media departments to push advertising and brand campaigns.

Participated in projects such as Floyd's Sticker Jam (Google Indie Latam 3rd place winner), Tough Coded: Live, Tower Power (on closed beta) and Boop Kids (TBR).

Peppermelon / Producer

FEBRUARY 2015 - FEBRUARY 2016 BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA

Worked closely with clients such as DU Telecom, FOX, Ceska Sporitelna Bank, amongst others.

Managed schedules, budgets and scripts as well as overseeing technically and artistically the outsourcing partners and in-house art direction team.

Freelance / Designer

MARCH 2011 - NOVEMBER 2014

BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA

Designed user interfaces for a variety of web projects and clients.

Education

Universidad de Palermo / Diseño de Imagen y Sonido (Image and Sound Design)

MARCH 2010 - DECEMBER 2014

BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA

Production / CG oriented. Won multiple awards for best of term projects.

Graduated with cum laude honors.

Image Campus / Visual Effects, Compositing

FEBRUARY 2013 - MARCH 2014 BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA

One year course for visual effects compositing and CG. Worked with Maya and Nuke.

Image Campus / Autodesk Maya Full

MARCH 2012 - MAY 2012

BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA

Two months course, in-depth Maya learning course.

Highlights

SKILLS

 Strong organizational skills
 Detail oriented
 Solid technical knowledge
 Able to adapt and work under pressure
 Innovative and problem solver
 Team oriented, strong management skills.

ACKNOWLEDGMENTS

16 awards and acknowledgements received between 2010 and 2014, including publications, best of term projects and short films.

GRADUATION PROJECT

"El trabajo del ilusionista" ("The illusionist's job") is my graduation project. A thesis presenting the demo-reel as a product for laboral insertion in the visual effects and animation industry.

Languages

SPANISH

Native speaker.

ENGLISH

Fluent in writing and speaking.